Music by Deuxvolt
www.deuxvolt.com
Add your own musics and lyrics files too
Many examples are included in the "music" directory
I'm walking away
Another day has died
I'm walking alone
I wish to dream again...
All I ask in this life
It's to find some place to rest
Inside my heart
Longing to disappear...
Many years without a sun
Wrapped in shadows of the past
It seems already written in the stars
No wind will be so cold
And no rain will be so hard...
(Bring to life)
I'm returned from death
(Have no fear)
Burning all the scariest ghosts
(Life's so frail)
In the sands of desert
(Against the stream)
In the deepest pit of mind
(Bring to life)
Where the days are dark
(Have no fear)
When the gravity's reversed
(Life's so frail)
Resist, be strong, don't stop, go fast!
(Against the stream)
Beyond the end!...
Beyond the end...