Little Drummer Boy
(Popular Christmas Song)
Boney M
Come, they told me
Pa rum pum pum pum
Our newborn King to see
Our finest gifts we´ll bring
Pa rum pum pum pum
To lay before the King
Pa rum pum pum pum - rum pum pum pum - rum pum pum pum
So, to honour Him
Pa rum pum pum pum
When we come
Baby Jesus
Pa rum pum pum pum
I am a poor boy too
I have no gift to bring
Pa rum pum pum pum
That's fit to give a King
Pa rum pum pum pum - rum pum pum pum - rum pum pum pum
Shall I play for you?
Pa rum pum pum pum
On my drum?
Mary nodded
Pa rum pum pum pum
The ox and lamb kept time
I played my drum for Him
Pa rum pum pum pum
I played my best for Him
Pa rum pum pum pum - rum pum pum pum - rum pum pum pum
Then He smiled at me
Pa rum pum pum pum
Me and my drum
Mary nodded
Pa rum pum pum pum
The ox and lamb kept time
I played my drum for Him
Pa rum pum pum pum
I played my best for Him
Pa rum pum pum pum - rum pum pum pum - rum pum pum pum
Then He smiled at me
Pa rum pum pum pum
Me and my drum